[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When was the first major use of tanks in a battle?", "correct_answer": "World War I - Nov 20, 1917", "incorrect_answers": ["World War I - Nov 20, 1914", "World War II - 1941", "World War I - Nov 20, 1918"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1655 the Bubonic Plague hit India and China causing mass casualties.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the highest point in the state of Illinois?", "correct_answer": "Charles Mound", "incorrect_answers": ["Lincoln Mound", "Devils Mound", "Mount Vernon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of seafood is put in the center of the traditional Japanese dumplings called Takoyaki?", "correct_answer": "Octopus", "incorrect_answers": ["Squid", "Shrimp", "Seaweed"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following versions of Blackjack is most favorable to the player?", "correct_answer": "Single deck game", "incorrect_answers": ["Two-deck game", "Eight-deck game", "Four-deck game"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of presents are considered to be taboo according to Russian superstition?", "correct_answer": "Sharp objects", "incorrect_answers": ["Perfumes", "Black objects", "Baby clothes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is a multiple fruit, just like the pineapple?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Mulberry", "Breadfruit", "Fig"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following states borders South Carolina?", "correct_answer": "Georgia", "incorrect_answers": ["Alabama", "Tennessee", "Virginia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The largest gay and lesbian rights march took place in the capital of this country.", "correct_answer": "The US", "incorrect_answers": ["The UK", "Canada", "France"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the special talent of the penguin Mumble from the 2006 animated movie Happy Feet?", "correct_answer": "Tap dancing", "incorrect_answers": ["Shoe making", "Singing", "Break dancing"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Unlike other ostriches, this subspecies of ostrich has small feathers on its head.", "correct_answer": "Masai Ostrich", "incorrect_answers": ["Arabian Ostrich", "Somali Ostrich", "North African Ostrich"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Botox (botulinum toxin) is used to treat which one of the following diseases?", "correct_answer": "Headache", "incorrect_answers": ["Congestive heart failure", "Pulmonary hypertension", "Kidney failure"]}]